Center for Traditional Music and Dance collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Event documentation, 1968-2015
  - Events, 1999
    - Folk Parks 1999, September 1999
      - Moving Images, 1999-09-25
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 99-0925-4
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 99-0925-5
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 99-0925-6
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 99-0925-7
      - Sound Recordings, 1999-09-25
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 99-0925_1; Note on media: CASYM (Caribbean American Sports and Yourth Movement Steel)
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 99-0925_2; Note on media: Kotchegna Dance Company
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 99-0925_3; Note on media: Coco Merenson
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 99-0925_4; Note on media: Yuri Yunakov
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 99-0925_5; Note on media: McCollough Sons of Thunder with Elder Edward Babb
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_99-0925-1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_99-0925-2
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_99-0925-3
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_99-0925-4
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_99-0925-5
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_99-09-25--5
        - 1 sound disc (CD), FP 99-0925-1; Note on media: CASYM Steel Band (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), FP 99-0925-2; Note on media: Kotchegna (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), FP 99-0925-3; Note on media: Coco Merenson (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), FP 99-0925-5; Note on media: McCollough Sons of Thunder (Box 16)
        - 14 audio files (wav): digital., FP99-0925_1
        - 4 audio files (wav): digital., FP99-0925_2
        - 7 audio files (wav): digital., FP99-0925_3
        - 11 audio file (wav): digital., FP99-0925 5
    - Other events, 1999
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1999-04-18, Note on folder: Nashi Traditsii (Box-folder 8/8)
        - 1 folder, 1999-05, Note on folder: Lincoln Center Out of Doors (Box-folder 8/9)
        - 1 folder, 1999-05-22, Note on folder: Community Cultures in Performance (Box-folder 8/10)
        - 1 folder, 1999-06-05, Note on folder: Kitchrie (Box-folder 8/12)
        - 1 folder, 1999-06-24, Note on folder: Fifth Annual Ralph Rinzler Memorial Concert (Box-folder 8/13)
        - 1 folder, 1999-08-08, Note on folder: Lincoln Center (Box-folder 8/15)
        - 1 folder, 1999-2000, Note on folder: Tradition Around the Corner (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Photographs
        - 1 folder, 1999-09, Note on folder: Tasla School (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Sound Recordings
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 125 min.), 1999-04-21, AFC 2014/044: CCI 99-0421_1; Note on media: Juan de Jesus Coco (founder, Coco Merenson)
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., 1999-04-21, CCI_99-0421-1
  - Events, 2000
    - Nashi Traditsii: A Celebration of Mountain Jewish Culture, February 2000
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2000-02-06
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Sound Recordings, 2000-02-06
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0206_1; Note on media: Yiddish art and popular song (presented by Michael Alpert)
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0206_2; Note on media: Yiddish art and popular song (presented by Michael Alpert), conclusion; Roots of klezmer workshop (presented by Michael Alpert)
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0206_3; Note on media: Roots of klezmer workshop (presented by Michael Alpert), conclusion
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0206_4
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0206_5; Note on media: Ensemble Shashmaqan; Di Molever Kompanye; Tereza Ensemble (continued)
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0206_6; Note on media: Tereza Ensemble (beginning; continued on CCI 00-0206_5)
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_00-0206_1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_00-0206_3
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_00-0206-1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_00-0206-2
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_00-0206-4
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_00-0206-5
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_00-0206-6
    - Pagbubunyi: A Celebration of Filipino Culture and Heritage, April 2000
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2000-04-02
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Moving Images, 2000-04-01 to 2000-04-02
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0402_1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0402_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 000401-1; Note on media: Pagbabunyi Workshop 4-5p.m.
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 000401-2; Note on media: Pagbubunyi Workshop Guitarist
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0402_1_2; Note on media: Washington Irving High School, music workshops within Pagbubunyi
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0402_v1_v2; Note on media: afternoon performance
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 00-0402-1&2-DV; Note on media: Music workshops within Pagbubunyi
      - Sound Recordings, 2000-04-02
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0402_1
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0402_2
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0402_3
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0402_4
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0402_5
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0402_6
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_00-0402-1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_00-0402-2
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_00-0402-3
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_00-0402_5
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_00-0402-6
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CTMD_00-04-02
    - Folk Parks 2000, September 2000
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2000-09-09
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 8/24)
      - Moving Images, 2000-09-08
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c1_t1; Note on media: Cheres
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c1_t3; Note on media: American Indian
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c1_t4; Note on media: Korea
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c1_t4a
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c1_t6
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c1_t7
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c2_t1; Note on media: Cheres
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c2_t2; Note on media: Bibak (?)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c2_t5
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c2_t6
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c2_t7
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0908_c2_t8
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c1_t1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c1_t2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c1_t3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c1_t4
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c1_4a
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c1_t6
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c1_t7
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c2_t1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c2_t2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c2_t2a
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c2_t4
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c2_t5
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c2_t6
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c2_t7
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FP 00-0908_c2_t8
      - Sound Recordings, 2000-09-09
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0909_1
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0909_3
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0909_4
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_00-0909-2
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., FP_00-0909-3
        - 1 sound disc (CD), FP 00-0909; Note on media: David David (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), FP 00-0909-1; Note on media: Cherish the Ladies (Box 16)
        - 3 audio files (wav): digital., FP00-0909
        - 13 audio files (wav): digital., FP00-0909-1
    - Other events, 2000
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 2000-05-20, Note on folder: Badenya (Box-folder 8/20)
        - 1 folder, 2000-06-25, Note on folder: Quisqueya (Box-folder 8/21)
        - 1 folder, 2000-08, Note on folder: Lincoln Center Out of Doors (Box-folder 8/22)
        - 1 folder, 2000-08-25, Note on folder: Kitchrie (Box-folder 8/23)
        - 1 folder, 2000-12-10, Note on folder: Tenth Albanian Festival (Box-folder 8/25)
      - Moving Images
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2000-09-02, AFC 2014/044: FP 00-0902_c1_t2
      - Sound Recordings
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., 2000-01-09, APAP_00-0109
        - 1 sound disc (CD), 2000-08-31, RS 00-0831; Note on media: Recording Session: Sau Family Boys (Box 17)
        - 9 audio files (wav): digital., 2000-08-31, RS00-0831
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., 2000-09-09, CTMD_00-09-09_1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., 2000-09-09, CTMD_00-09-09-4
  - Events, 2001
    - Association of Performing Arts Presenters (APAP) Showcase, January 2001
      - Sound Recordings, 2001-01-06 to 2001-01-09
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: APAP 01-0106
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., APAP_01-0106
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: APAP 01-0109
    - 4th annual Nashi Traditsii, April 2001
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2001-04-01
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 8/26)
      - Moving Images, 2001-04-01
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0401_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0401_3
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0401_4
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0401_5
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 00-0401_6
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 01-0401_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 01-0401; Note on media: Di Molever Kompanye, Shashmaqam, Ensemble Tereza
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 01-0401_05
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 01-0401_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 01-0401_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 01-0401_3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 01-0401_4
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 01-0401_6
      - Sound Recordings, 2001-04-01
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 01-0401_1
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 01-0401_2
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 01-0401_3
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 01-0401_4
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 01-0401_5
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_01-0401-1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_01-0401-2
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_01-0401-3
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_01-0401-4
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_01-0401-5-DO
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 01-0401-1; Note on media: Di Molever Kompanye, Shashmaqam, Ensemble Tereza (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 01-0401-2; Note on media: Di Molever Kompanye, Shashmaqam, Ensemble Tereza (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 01-0401-3; Note on media: Di Molever Kompanye, Shashmaqam, Ensemble Tereza (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 01-0401-4; Note on media: Di Molever Kompanye, Shashmaqam, Ensemble Tereza (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 01-0401-5; Note on media: German Goldenstyn, Hersh Rikelman, Mikail Shenderov, Yefim Aptekar (Box 15)
        - 18 audio files (wav): digital., CCI01-0401-1
        - 17 audio files (wav): digital., CCI01-0401-2
        - 15 audio files (wav): digital., CCI01-0401-3
        - 3 audio files (wav): digital., CCI01-0401-4
        - 8 audio files (wav): digital., CCI01-0401-5
    - Mano a Mano, December 2001
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2001-12-16
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Sound Recordings, 2001-12-16
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 01-1216-CD1; Note on media: Mariachi Assoc. of NY and Guillermo Velasquez (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 01-1216-CD2; Note on media: G. Velasquez / Conjunto Hueyapan (Box 15)
        - 33 audio files (wav): digital., CCI 01-1216
    - Other events, 2001
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 2001-05-02, Note on folder: Pasasalamat (Box-folder 9/1)
        - 1 folder, 2001-05-16, Note on folder: Abdoulaye Diabate at WFC Winter Garden (Box-folder 9/2)
        - 1 folder, 2001-06-12, Note on folder: New York City: Global Beat of the Boroughs (Box-folder 9/3)
        - 1 oversize folder, 2001-06-12, Note on media: New York City: Global Beat of the Boroughs (Container oversize folder 1)
        - 1 folder, 2001-06-17, Note on folder: Quisqueya (Box-folder 9/4)
        - 1 oversize folder, 2001-06-17, Note on media: Quisqueya (Container oversize folder 1)
        - 1 folder, 2001-06-27, Note on folder: Smithsonian Folklife Festival (Box-folder 9/5)
        - 1 folder, 2001-08, Note on folder: Lincoln Center Out of Doors (Box-folder 9/6)
        - 1 folder, 2001, Note on folder: Folk Parks (Box-folder 9/7)
        - 1 folder, 2001-11-11, Note on folder: Eleventh Albanian Festival (Box-folder 9/8)
        - 1 folder, 2001-2002, Note on folder: Roster CTMD (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Moving Images
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2001-10-03, AFC 2014/044: FP 01-1003_1; Note on media: Day of the Dead, part 1; Theatre production by Miguel Cossio
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., 2001-10-03, FP 01-1003_1
      - Sound Recordings
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., 2001-04-28, WFMU_01-0428-1
        - 1 sound disc (CD), 2001-11-29, INT 01-1129; Note on media: Interview with USOPAY Cadar by Tom Van Buren (Box 16)
        - 14 audio files (wav): digital., 2001-11-29, INT 01-1129
  - Events, 2002
    - World Music Showcase, January 2002
      - Moving Images, 2002-01-13
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: APAP 02-0113_1; Note on media: Retumba; Los Macondos
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: APAP 02-0113_2; Note on media: Shashmaqam
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: APAP 02-0113_3; Note on media: Andy Statman Trio; Tokovnov
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: APAP 02-0113_4; Note on media: Kotchegna
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: APAP 02-0113_5; Note on media: Los Macondos; Shashmaqam
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: APAP 02-0113_6; Note on media: Andy Statman Trio; Tokovnov
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: APAP 02-0113_7; Note on media: Kotchegna
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., APAP 02-0113_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., APAP 02-0113_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., APAP 02-0113_3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., APAP 02-0113_4
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., APAP 02-0113_5
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., APAP 02-0113_6
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., APAP 02-0113_7
    - Pagbubunyi: A Celebration of Filipino Culture and Heritage, February 2002
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2002-02-23
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Moving Images, 2002-02-23
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 63 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-0223_t1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-0223_t1_dv1; Note on media: Manta Gowani
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 63 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-0223_t2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 90 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-0223_t2_dv2; Note on media: Manta Gowani
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 02-0223_t1_dv2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 02-0223_t2_dv2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 02-02223-2MantaGowani
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 02-0223
      - Sound Recordings, 2002-02-23
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 65 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-0223_1; Note on media: FIT Auditorium [Fashion Institute of Technology]
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-0223_1; Note on media: Maranao dance (kapmalo-malong); Maguindanaon ensemble (duyog); Maraho/Maguindanaon; Tagongko/Tagonggo (first half of show)
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-0223_2; Note on media: second half of show
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-0223_3; Note on media: rehearsal
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_020223
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_020223
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_020223-1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI-020223-2
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_02-0223-3
    - Nashi Traditsii: Crossing Bridges Jewish Musical Worlds of the Former Soviet Union, May 2002
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2002-05-19
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Sound Recordings, 2002-05-19
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-0519; Note on media: ADAT #1 and DAT rough mix
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-0519_1
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-0519_2
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-0519_3
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_02-0519-1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_02-0519-4
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_02-0519-5
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_020519-2
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., CCI_020519-3
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 02-0519-1 (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), CCI 02-0519-2 (Box 15)
        - 17 audio files (wav): digital., CCI020519-1
        - 10 audio files (wav): digital., CCI020519-2
    - Festi-Andes, August 2002
      - Moving Images, 2002-08-25
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-08-25_1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 02-08-25_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 02-0825 Tape 1/2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 02-0825 Tape 2/2
    - New York World Festival: Music Around the Mediterranean, September 2002
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2002-09-20
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Moving Images, 2002-09-20 to 2002-09-22
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0920_2; Note on media: Lauruddas; Radio Tarifa, part 1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0920_3; Note on media: Radio Tarifa, part 2; Giglio Brass Band
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0920_3; Note on media: Radio Tarifa, part 2; Giglio Brass Band
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0920_4a
        - 1 video disc (DVD), NYWF 02-0921 DVD; Note on media: Merita Halili/Raif Hyseni (Box 19)
        - 1 video disc (DVD), NYWF 02-0921 DVD; Note on media: Merita Halili/Raif Hyseni (Box 19)
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF_02-0921-DVD_title01
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF_02-0921-DVD_title02
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF_02-0921-DVD_title03
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0921_4; Note on media: Lauruddas; Radio Tarifa
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0921_5A; Note on media: Radio Tarifa, part 2, Klapa Astoria; Naji Youssef, part 1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0921_5B; Note on media: Naji Youseff, part 2; Aramire
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0921_6; Note on media: Aramire (end); Boban Markovic; Kemani Cemal, part 1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0921_7; Note on media: Kemani Cemal, part 2; Merita Halili, part 1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0921_8; Note on media: Merita Halili, part 2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0921_4; Note on media: Lauruddas; Radio Tarifa
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0921_5A; Note on media: Radio Tarifa, part 2, Klapa Astoria; Naji Youssef, part 1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0921_5B; Note on media: Naji Youseff, part 2; Aramire
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0921_6; Note on media: Aramire (end); Boban Markovic; Kemani Cemal, part 1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0921_7; Note on media: Kemani Cemal, part 2; Merita Halili, part 1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0921_8; Note on media: Merita Halili, part 2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0922_9; Note on media: Shoshana Tubi; Gadwa; Sout al Ghonba [?]; Bosnian dance
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0922_10; Note on media: Bosnian dance, part 2; Mikrokosmos, part 1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0922_11; Note on media: Mikrokosmos; Greek dance; Ilios Kementzides
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0922_12; Note on media: Greek dance, part 2; Zakia, part 1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0922_13; Note on media: Zakia, part 2; NEME, part 1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: NYWF 02-0922_14; Note on media: NEME, part 2; Kemani Cemal
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0922_9; Note on media: Shoshana Tubi; Gadwa; Sout al Ghonba [?]; Bosnian dance
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0922_10; Note on media: Bosnian dance, part 2; Mikrokosmos, part 1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0922_11; Note on media: Mikrokosmos; Greek dance; Ilios Kementzides
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0922_12; Note on media: Greek dance, part 2; Zakia, part 1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0922_13; Note on media: Zakia, part 2; Near Eastern Music Ensemble (NEME), part 1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., NYWF 02-0922_14; Note on media: Near Eastern Music Ensemble (NEME), part 2; Kemani Cemal
      - Sound Recordings, 2002-09-20 to 2002-09-21
        - 1 sound disc (CD), NYWF 02-0920; Note on media: Workshop: The Mediterranean Voice (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), NYWF 02-0920-1; Note on media: ARAMIRE (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), NYWF 02-0920-2; Note on media: Launeddas/RADIO TARIFA (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), NYWF 02-0920-3; Note on media: RADIO TARIFA (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), NYWF 02-0920-4; Note on media: Giglio Band/Launeddas (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), NYWF 02-0920-6,7; Note on media: Naji Youseff & NEME/ARAMIRE (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), NYWF 02-0920-8; Note on media: Boban Markovic/Kemani Cemal I (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), NYWF 02-0920-12; Note on media: Bosnians (end)/Mikroksomos (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), NYWF 02-0920-13; Note on media: Greek Dance I/Ilias Kementzedes/Chris Fasarakis (Box 16)